<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hippocampus on Tom George</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hippocampus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hippocampus on Tom George</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.2</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/hippocampus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Replay of procedural experience is independent of the hippocampus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/papers/ppseqreplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/papers/ppseqreplay/</guid>
      <description>We use an unsupervised sequence detection algorithm to demonstrate, for the first time, replay of procedural memories in the striatum and that this replay is hippocampus-independent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A generative model of the hippocampal formation trained with theta driven local learning rules</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/papers/helmholtzhippocampus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/papers/helmholtzhippocampus/</guid>
      <description>A model of the hippocampal formation where theta-band oscillations and local error-correcting Hebbian learning rules train weights it analagous to a wake-speel algorithm. This bioplausible hippocampal model replicates key cognitive functions including path integration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RatInABox, a toolkit for modelling locomotion and neuronal activity in continuous environments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/papers/ratinabox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/papers/ratinabox/</guid>
      <description>This paper documents and motivates the RatInABox package, used for modellign locomotion and neural activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid learning of predictive maps with STDP and theta phase precession</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/papers/stdpsr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/papers/stdpsr/</guid>
      <description>We study how successor representations can be learned in a biologically plausible way by hippocampal neurons using STDP and theta phase procession.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
